<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>social networks on mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/social-networks/</link><description>Recent content in social networks on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:44:07 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/social-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finding My Way Out of the Network Tunnel.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/network-ahh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:44:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/network-ahh/</guid><description>I wrote up an incomplete, 16+ paragraph discussion about the kind of social network I would like to see, before realizing that even I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I want. In my head, I want everything to be clean and tidy — one network that did everything. Created great, strong communities, answered questions about various issues, felt tight-knit and allowed for reasonable discussions, all very pie-in-the-sky. But I don&amp;rsquo;t think these can be relegated to one network, nor should they.</description></item><item><title>Accepting Different Terms.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:23:06 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been increasing scrutiny placed on social media over the past decade, from all angles. Criticisms of their practices of election meddling, attention-stealing, data collecting, and generally being cesspools of humanity. Many of these companies have created walled gardens that discourage platform departure and have been optimized to be as attention-grabbing as possible. After all, more usage generates greater revenue, even if it&amp;rsquo;s at the detriment of a beneficial experience for the user.</description></item></channel></rss>