<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/</link><description>Recent content on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 16:27:38 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Intrinsic Bliss of Walking Your Groceries Home.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/walking/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 16:27:38 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/walking/</guid><description>Southern California is about driving. To get to any place, you need to drive, find someone who can drive, or navigate the often slow and dismal public transit routes, all of which I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced in excess, first-hand. Although it sounds relatively negative, I enjoyed this. Driving is something I love because, especially early-on in my life, it provides this immense feeling of freedom and control, despite everything else being in disarray.</description></item><item><title>The Right Tools.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tools/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 14:02:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tools/</guid><description>It can be difficult to identify whether anxiety can simply be overcome through thought or a shift in thinking. Given that it&amp;rsquo;s literally in the mind, what is the difference between a healthy mind and one that overthinks? Mental disorders in general are fuzzy, and somewhat undefined as they manifest differently in everyone. This can make me somewhat skeptical of our understanding of psychology because it seems so undefined, and we don&amp;rsquo;t know and can&amp;rsquo;t observe those interactions.</description></item><item><title>Something Important to Me.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 22:35:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/start/</guid><description>I used to be obsessed with the idea of legacy. This concept was pervasive — I couldn&amp;rsquo;t let go of wanting to be important or wanting to be recognized as important. This idea stuck with me for years, despite not actually working towards greatness or high achievement.
I think when you&amp;rsquo;re especially young, it can be easy to succumb to the ego and seek to defeat death, something intangible and scary.</description></item></channel></rss>