<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/</link><description>Recent content on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What If It Went Right.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/serendipity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/serendipity/</guid><description>About two weeks ago, I made the fun, but somewhat draining 7 hour drive from here to EDC on my own. Although I usually go to festivals with friends, I had committed to the 3-day, 32 combined hour undertaking because I was astounded the first time I went. The first view I had of the festival was incredible in its scale — tens of thousands of people, more than a dozen stages, and intricate design across the entire speedway, and I could see it all from where I stood.</description></item><item><title>Missing Dreams.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/dreams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/dreams/</guid><description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think I have dreams. There aren&amp;rsquo;t any specific goals I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to reach for, and I wonder if that resonates with others. Having dreams, especially distinct ones, is often portrayed in America. But perhaps as a byproduct of my aimlessness, I seem to lack any.
I want goals to aim for. I think a lack of direction is a result of vague and undefined endpoints. Having daily flexibility and stable income is not a dream — it&amp;rsquo;s more survival and not wanting to waste away precariously at a suboptimal job.</description></item><item><title>Decisions.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/decisions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:44:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/decisions/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to figure out exactly what I want to do. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for jobs — with little success — and slowly draining my savings. I also read that I may have to start paying off the student loans of which I am wholly unequipped, given the above situation. What a pain.
Over the past year, I&amp;rsquo;ve told myself and others that while I&amp;rsquo;m young, I want to be flexible and not completely tied down to a place.</description></item><item><title>Happier.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/happier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:31:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/happier/</guid><description>Life has strong ups and downs, it&amp;rsquo;s a given. I know that there is no state of being, nothing to reach that provides a constant, unending source of happiness, which seems sad. I want to reach a place in my life where I have a stable, happy life, with dips, yes, but not drop-offs where I feel aimless, depressed, and empty, for long periods. Human psychology and the hedonic treadmill have proven that much.</description></item><item><title>Self-Respect &amp; Selfishness.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/respect/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 23:43:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/respect/</guid><description>In the journey of gaining self-respect, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to tell myself I&amp;rsquo;m being selfish. Many times when I&amp;rsquo;ve stood up for myself, I&amp;rsquo;ve been convinced that my position is unreasonable or that I&amp;rsquo;m asking for too much. So now, when I get pushback from what I think is speaking my truth, I fold much more easily because I&amp;rsquo;m so unsure of my beliefs and not confident enough in myself.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this is an excuse I tell myself, as to not become unreasonable or selfish, or instead if I&amp;rsquo;m just holding myself back with old beliefs.</description></item><item><title>Releasing the Tethers.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tethers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:03:23 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tethers/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that what&amp;rsquo;s caused me a ton of anguish is attaching a portion of my identity to inherently unstable and impermanent states. If those states change, as they do, I find it excruciating and impossible to function, because I feel as if a portion of me is destroyed in the process. It means that I will cling to these ephemeral states and force them, even when they are due to change, always to my own detriment or the detriment of others.</description></item><item><title>Appreciation: The 'Scaring the Hoes' Album.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/appreciation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/appreciation/</guid><description>My Top 3 Songs On Scaring the Hoes Burfict! - Track 6/14 I really like this track because it is so bombastic straight from the beginning. Horns blaring, a thumping bass, and a really strong, addictive chorus from Danny Brown. Additionally, JPEGmafia&amp;rsquo;s flow at the start of his verse sounds great.
SCARING THE HOES by JPEGMAFIA x Danny Brown Kingdom Hearts Key (ft. redveil) - Track 9/14 I think the sample on this track sounds really beautiful.</description></item><item><title>Everything Can Be Found Here.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/babel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 02:38:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/babel/</guid><description>A long time ago I came across the Library of Babel. It&amp;rsquo;s based on a book, that I haven&amp;rsquo;t read, centered around an infinite library, containing every possible set of text imaginable. That means that although nearly all of the library contains gibberish, there are some books that contain a perfect transcript of the future, bibliographies of every human being, and any other text that can ever be written.
The website replicates that concept.</description></item><item><title>Taking Action.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/problems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/problems/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that I&amp;rsquo;ve had so much anxiety, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been so focused on eliminating it that when I feel normal, acceptable levels of stress, I interpret it as unnecessary and unwanted, when instead it&amp;rsquo;s more of call to action than an irrational feeling.
Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve gained better control over the way I feel and process stress, anxiety can feel more acute when it does happen because my brain is saying, &amp;ldquo;Why isn&amp;rsquo;t this just going away?</description></item><item><title>Processing it All.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/too-much/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 13:09:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/too-much/</guid><description>I think it&amp;rsquo;s easy to fill compelled to capture as much knowledge as possible. I always want to go through all my RSS feeds, read every article that seems remotely interesting, and be complete by the end of the day. More information, however, just isn&amp;rsquo;t helpful. Constantly we are inundated with data and the idea that we must always be consuming. It&amp;rsquo;s accepted as the baseline, but it&amp;rsquo;s honestly exhausting to actually do, if you think about it.</description></item><item><title>New Beliefs.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/changing-brain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:47:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/changing-brain/</guid><description>Over the past few months, I have done some extensive introspection. Because I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of time on my hands, it&amp;rsquo;s become much, much easier to feel every little pang that comes about, and there is much less to distract me. In that time, I&amp;rsquo;ve realized how strong this constant, incessant background anxiety was that I&amp;rsquo;ve been carrying around. Even in times of ease and safety, I still found it gripping ahold and refusing to let go.</description></item><item><title>The Unsatisfying Answer.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/network-ahh/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:44:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/network-ahh/</guid><description>I wrote up an incomplete, 16+ paragraph discussion about the kind of social network I would like to see, before realizing that even I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I want. In my head, I want everything to be clean and tidy — one network that did everything. Created great, strong communities, answered questions about various issues, felt tight-knit and allowed for reasonable discussions, all very pie-in-the-sky. But I don&amp;rsquo;t think these can be relegated to one network, nor should they.</description></item><item><title>Incomplete: What Do I Want From Online Society?</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/social-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/social-networks/</guid><description>In general, I&amp;rsquo;m someone that has always been interested in, and thinks a lot about systems, and what they incentivise based on their structure. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s in terms of governments, sports, urban design, websites, or any other system that revolves around human interaction. Lately, that focus, as you may have seen has been on social networks.
As of late, I&amp;rsquo;ve heavily researched alternative ideas for social networks. This is mostly inspired by my interest in privacy and trying to understand how these social networks affect society at large.</description></item><item><title>Accepting Different Terms.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:23:06 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been increasing scrutiny placed on social media over the past decade, from all angles. Criticisms of their practices of election meddling, attention-stealing, data collecting, and generally being cesspools of humanity. Many of these companies have created walled gardens that discourage platform departure and have been optimized to be as attention-grabbing as possible. After all, more usage generates greater revenue, even if it&amp;rsquo;s at the detriment of a beneficial experience for the user.</description></item><item><title>Reality through Perception.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/mindcontrol/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 01:06:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/mindcontrol/</guid><description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to arrive at the idea that there is a significant distinction between how our brain perceives reality, and how reality actually is. It&amp;rsquo;s always been my assumption that what I&amp;rsquo;m seeing and feeling represents the reality of the situation I&amp;rsquo;m in. If I&amp;rsquo;m disappointed or frustrated, it&amp;rsquo;s because the situation is objectively disappointing or frustrating. I have come to find that this belief is often false.
When I perceive a situation, my senses attempt to provide the most accurate, objective version of reality, minimizing their own biases as much as possible.</description></item><item><title>The Intrinsic Bliss of Walking to the Store.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/walking/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 16:27:38 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/walking/</guid><description>Southern California is about driving. To get to any place, you need to drive, find someone who can drive, or navigate the often slow and dismal public transit routes, all of which I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced in excess, first-hand. Although it sounds relatively negative, I enjoyed this. Driving is something I love because, especially early on in my life, it provides this immense feeling of freedom and control, despite everything else being in disarray.</description></item><item><title>It's All In Your Head.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tools/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 14:02:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tools/</guid><description>It can be difficult to identify whether anxiety can simply be overcome through thought or a shift in thinking. Given that it&amp;rsquo;s literally in the mind, what is the difference between a healthy mind and one that overthinks? Mental disorders in general are fuzzy, and somewhat undefined as they manifest differently in everyone. This can make me somewhat skeptical of our understanding of psychology because it seems so undefined, and we don&amp;rsquo;t know and can&amp;rsquo;t observe those interactions.</description></item><item><title>Something Important to Me.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 22:35:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/start/</guid><description>I used to be obsessed with the idea of legacy. This concept was pervasive — I couldn&amp;rsquo;t let go of wanting to be important or wanting to be recognized as important. This idea stuck with me for years, despite not actually working towards greatness or high achievement.
I think when you&amp;rsquo;re especially young, it can be easy to succumb to the ego and seek to defeat death, something intangible and scary.</description></item></channel></rss>