<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advice on mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/advice/</link><description>Recent content in Advice on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 20:42:36 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Course Correction.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/course-correction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 20:42:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/course-correction/</guid><description>Everyday, it feels like I&amp;rsquo;m failing to correct. I have a list of all my biggest issues, I&amp;rsquo;m aware of what needs to change, but I don&amp;rsquo;t take the steps to fix it. It&amp;rsquo;s so easy for me to just keep following the same patterns, without adjusting anything, but recently more than usual, I&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing a voice that&amp;rsquo;s asking me to make these changes. I need to start taking small, consistent steps so I can stay on top of what I need to do.</description></item><item><title>Finding My Way.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rhythm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:06:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rhythm/</guid><description>Despite the last post, I&amp;rsquo;m still struggling to find that rhythm. I realized I&amp;rsquo;m holding myself back significantly in multiple ways. I haven&amp;rsquo;t worked on my confidence in any major way, and that&amp;rsquo;s slowing me. Adding to that is my ability to make excuses for not starting anything. The only way to get better is to put in consistent work. Whether I want to make music, write, skate, or improve my mental health — I have to stick to it.</description></item><item><title>Finding the Keys to Happiness and Forgetting Where You Placed Them.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/reset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 20:47:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/reset/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute
Every time my life gets thrown out of wack — even in a good way — I forget the key ingredient that always makes things better. Even when I do remember, I forget the second most important part. Routine always provides me guidance. Feeling lost is one of the feelings that&amp;rsquo;s most constant in my life, and it&amp;rsquo;s one of the more unpleasant feelings that I get.</description></item></channel></rss>