<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Incentives on mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/incentives/</link><description>Recent content in Incentives on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:51:32 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/incentives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thoughts on the Killing of Brian Thompson.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/unitedhealth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:51:32 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/unitedhealth/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have a lot of thoughts about the recent killing of Brian Thompson. The reaction online, sadly, is extremely positive and to some degree, I can understand the reaction. When healthcare in America is so severely screwed up, the blame to a large extent is on these huge profit making entities. But I believe this reaction is both disturbing and misguided.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These companies are heinous in their treatment of their customers. Leaving so many in horrible situations, in the worst (and unfortunately, extremely common) cases, patients are left with both pain and crushing debt, which feed into each other. But they are not the flaws in the system, exploiting people because they are operating as vigilantes. They are the system that the government has allowed to prosper, with lawmakers ultimately being responsible for allowing their practices to go completely unchecked, and the most disadvantaged are left holding the bag.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>WIP: What Do I Want From Online Society?</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/social-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/social-networks/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In general, I&amp;rsquo;m someone that has always been interested in, and thinks a lot about systems, and what they incentivise based on their structure. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s in terms of governments, sports, urban design, websites, or any other system that revolves around human interaction. Lately, that focus, as you may have &lt;a href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives" title="Accepting Different Terms. | mental excess.">seen&lt;/a> has been on social networks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As of late, I&amp;rsquo;ve heavily researched &lt;a href="https://knightcolumbia.org/content/protocols-not-platforms-a-technological-approach-to-free-speech" title="Protocols, Not Platforms: A Technological Approach to Free Speech">alternative ideas&lt;/a> for social networks. This is mostly inspired by my interest in privacy and trying to understand how these social networks affect society at large. Although I&amp;rsquo;m not an incredibly active participant on social media, I can see how nuance is removed from concepts and ideas and then spread around quickly, informing us with a twisted, misrepresented version of reality. Additionally, I think its had a measurable negative impact on attention-spans.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Drive Revived.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rebooted/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 19:14:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rebooted/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve rediscovered my love for discussing society, incentives, structures, and philosophy that I encountered most while at college. And it made me realize, I can&amp;rsquo;t just listen and reflect upon the ills of society. The problems aren&amp;rsquo;t hypothetical — they involve real people that face these issues each day. Perhaps I can&amp;rsquo;t change the world, but I believe I can effect change locally. On the other hand, maybe dreaming big is worthwhile, because I should wring out any potential from the future I may have. Most importantly, it&amp;rsquo;s not enough to believe in ideals, I need to stand by them.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Accepting Different Terms.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:23:06 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</guid><description>&lt;p>There&amp;rsquo;s been increasing scrutiny placed on social media over the past decade, from all angles. Criticisms of their practices of election meddling, attention-stealing, data collecting, and generally being cesspools of humanity. Many of these companies have created walled gardens that discourage platform departure and have been optimized to be as attention-grabbing as possible. After all, more usage generates greater revenue, even if it&amp;rsquo;s at the detriment of a beneficial experience for the user.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>