<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>discovery on mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/discovery/</link><description>Recent content in discovery on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:03:23 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/discovery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tethers</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tethers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:03:23 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tethers/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that what&amp;rsquo;s caused me a ton of anguish is attaching a portion of my identity to inherently unstable and impermanent states. If those states change, as they do, I find it excruciating and impossible to function, because I feel as if a portion of me is destroyed in the process. It means that I will cling to these ephemeral states and force them, even when they are due to change, always to my own detriment or the detriment of others.</description></item><item><title>Taking Action.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/problems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/problems/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that I&amp;rsquo;ve had so much anxiety, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been so focused on eliminating it that when I feel normal, acceptable levels of stress, I interpret it as unnecessary and unwanted, when instead it&amp;rsquo;s more of call to action than an irrational feeling.
Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve gained better control over the way I feel and process stress, anxiety can feel more acute when it does happen because my brain is saying, &amp;ldquo;Why isn&amp;rsquo;t this just going away?</description></item><item><title>New Beliefs.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/changing-brain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:47:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/changing-brain/</guid><description>Over the past few months, I have done some extensive introspection. Because I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of time on my hands, it&amp;rsquo;s become much, much easier to feel every little pang that comes about, and there is much less to distract me. In that time, I&amp;rsquo;ve realized how strong this constant, incessant background anxiety was that I&amp;rsquo;ve been carrying around. Even in times of ease and safety, I still found it gripping ahold and refusing to let go.</description></item><item><title>Reality through Perception.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/mindcontrol/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 01:06:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/mindcontrol/</guid><description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to arrive at the idea that there is a significant distinction between how our brain perceives reality, and how reality actually is. It&amp;rsquo;s always been my assumption that what I&amp;rsquo;m seeing and feeling represents the reality of the situation I&amp;rsquo;m in. If I&amp;rsquo;m disappointed or frustrated, it&amp;rsquo;s because the situation is objectively disappointing or frustrating. I have come to find that this belief is often false.
When I perceive a situation, my senses attempt to provide the most accurate, objective version of reality, minimizing their own biases as much as possible.</description></item></channel></rss>