<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Change on mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/change/</link><description>Recent content in Change on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:51:32 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/tags/change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thoughts on the Killing of Brian Thompson.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/unitedhealth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:51:32 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/unitedhealth/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have a lot of thoughts about the recent killing of Brian Thompson. The reaction online, sadly, is extremely positive and to some degree, I can understand the reaction. When healthcare in America is so severely screwed up, the blame to a large extent is on these huge profit making entities. But I believe this reaction is both disturbing and misguided.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These companies are heinous in their treatment of their customers. Leaving so many in horrible situations, in the worst (and unfortunately, extremely common) cases, patients are left with both pain and crushing debt, which feed into each other. But they are not the flaws in the system, exploiting people because they are operating as vigilantes. They are the system that the government has allowed to prosper, with lawmakers ultimately being responsible for allowing their practices to go completely unchecked, and the most disadvantaged are left holding the bag.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Course Correction.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/course-correction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 20:42:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/course-correction/</guid><description>&lt;p>Everyday, it feels like I&amp;rsquo;m failing to correct. I have a list of all my biggest issues, I&amp;rsquo;m aware of what needs to change, but I don&amp;rsquo;t take the steps to fix it. It&amp;rsquo;s so easy for me to just keep following the same patterns, without adjusting anything, but recently more than usual, I&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing a voice that&amp;rsquo;s asking me to make these changes. I need to start taking small, consistent steps so I can stay on top of what I need to do.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>