<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on mental excess.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on mental excess.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:51:32 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thoughts on the Killing of Brian Thompson.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/unitedhealth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:51:32 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/unitedhealth/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have a lot of thoughts about the recent killing of Brian Thompson. The reaction online, sadly, is extremely positive and to some degree, I can understand the reaction. When healthcare in America is so severely screwed up, the blame to a large extent is on these huge profit making entities. But I believe this reaction is both disturbing and misguided.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These companies are heinous in there treatment of their customers. Leaving so many in horrible situations, in the worst (and unfortunately, extremely common) cases, patients are left with both pain and crushing debt, which feed into each other. But they are not the flaws in the system, exploiting people because they are operating as vigilantes. They are the system that the government has allowed to prosper, with lawmakers ultimately being responsible for allowing their practices to go completely unchecked, and the most disadvantaged are left holding the bag.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>WIP: What Do I Want From Online Society?</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/social-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/social-networks/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In general, I&amp;rsquo;m someone that has always been interested in, and thinks a lot about systems, and what they incentivise based on their structure. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s in terms of governments, sports, urban design, websites, or any other system that revolves around human interaction. Lately, that focus, as you may have &lt;a href="https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives" title="Accepting Different Terms. | mental excess.">seen&lt;/a> has been on social networks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As of late, I&amp;rsquo;ve heavily researched &lt;a href="https://knightcolumbia.org/content/protocols-not-platforms-a-technological-approach-to-free-speech" title="Protocols, Not Platforms: A Technological Approach to Free Speech">alternative ideas&lt;/a> for social networks. This is mostly inspired by my interest in privacy and trying to understand how these social networks affect society at large. Although I&amp;rsquo;m not an incredibly active participant on social media, I can see how nuance is removed from concepts and ideas and then spread around quickly, informing us with a twisted, misrepresented version of reality. Additionally, I think its had a measurable negative impact on attention-spans.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Re-learning.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/re-learning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:38:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/re-learning/</guid><description>&lt;p>Now that I have a bit more focus, I&amp;rsquo;m finding it difficult to concentrate on creating. I want to create, I have a draw to do so (even if slightly dampened compared to the past), and I have more time that I&amp;rsquo;ve both found and carved out. But I&amp;rsquo;ve been away from all my creative outlets for so long that I feel both aimless and daunted.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Most recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been consuming mountains of information, encouraging me to think about a wide range of topics, from the more narrow such as screentime and personal media consumption, to the broader concepts of government structure and city planning. So many ideas that aren&amp;rsquo;t fully formed, thoughts that are incomplete about fixing broken systems and designing better ones, best maximizing my time, and creating better environments to help myself.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Many Paths.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/many-paths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:10:16 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/many-paths/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s slow going but I&amp;rsquo;m finding some direction. Each decision I make reinforces a path. It&amp;rsquo;s opportunity cost but supercharged, in that one decision can rule out other options, but by choosing something over another in reinforces that behavior to the brain. The question isn&amp;rsquo;t how to have pure willpower to do make the right decisions, although that is certainly a part of it, the question is how to shape my life to incentive the right decisions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Breaking Through.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/breaking-thru/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 23:57:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/breaking-thru/</guid><description>&lt;p>I think it&amp;rsquo;s important for me to remember all the things I&amp;rsquo;d like to do. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to forget and become an amorphous blob navigating through life and losing all the things that provide purpose. And it happens in subtle ways, when I get out of practice I lose the skills to further my ability to do those things I&amp;rsquo;d like to do.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Like writing. I don&amp;rsquo;t just want to wait until the perfect storm of motivation and inspiration collide for me to practice writing, reading, meditating, cooking, programming, working out, and making music. These are all things I really appreciate and &lt;em>want&lt;/em> to do! There is no reason I should lose them to overwhelm, distractions, or general malaise in my life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The In Between.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/in-between/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 19:36:33 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/in-between/</guid><description>&lt;p>Turns out every empty platitude might be true after all. I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling lost recently, really lost. I feel out of balance and unable to stabilize anything in my life. I just want some semblance of control and every measure that I take feels like it&amp;rsquo;s not quite enough to shift that balance. I was reminded today, listening to a &lt;a href="https://megaphone.link/VMP2076192826" title="Life is hard. Can philosophy help? | The Gray Area with Sean Illing">podcast&lt;/a> that most of our lives is spend aiming for goals. But it&amp;rsquo;s a paradoxical activity, because we spend time in anticipation of reaching that goal, waiting for it to provide us what we want, to make us happy. But when we reach it, it suddenly becomes the past and no longer can bring us what we want. Our time is much better used if we learn to like the doing, which does not at all mean that the doing always needs to make us happy. Part of the doing is experiencing difficult and sometimes terrible things. But goals don&amp;rsquo;t provide us with much at all.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Course Correction.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/course-correction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 20:42:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/course-correction/</guid><description>&lt;p>Everyday, it feels like I&amp;rsquo;m failing to correct. I have a list of all my biggest issues, I&amp;rsquo;m aware of what needs to change, but I don&amp;rsquo;t take the steps to fix it. It&amp;rsquo;s so easy for me to just keep following the same patterns, without adjusting anything, but recently more than usual, I&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing a voice that&amp;rsquo;s asking me to make these changes. I need to start taking small, consistent steps so I can stay on top of what I need to do.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Escape the House.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/discovery/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:09:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/discovery/</guid><description>&lt;p>I think I&amp;rsquo;ve found the solution for my life that both provides me with change and structure at the same time. It&amp;rsquo;s not a revolutionary idea, but now that I&amp;rsquo;ve tried it, I think it&amp;rsquo;s really important. Having scheduled time for pushing myself, doing something out of my comfort zone allows me to both keep my routines and push myself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My natural inclination is to stay inside as much as possible, which feels safe, but I think I feel about as anxious when I stay inside as when I do something new. It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult hurtle to overcome, but every time I push myself to be alone and just GO, I feel better about myself. It gives me motivation and drive, it feels scary at first, but then refreshing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Finding My Way.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rhythm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:06:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rhythm/</guid><description>&lt;p>Despite the last post, I&amp;rsquo;m still struggling to find that rhythm. I realized I&amp;rsquo;m holding myself back significantly in multiple ways. I haven&amp;rsquo;t worked on my confidence in any major way, and that&amp;rsquo;s slowing me. Adding to that is my ability to make excuses for not starting anything. The only way to get better is to put in consistent work. Whether I want to make music, write, skate, or improve my mental health — I have to stick to it. Any habits I want to break, I have to make an effort to do because the default is to keep following the same paths that I&amp;rsquo;ve already instilled.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Keys to Happiness and Forgetting Where You Placed Them.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/reset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 20:47:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/reset/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every time my life gets thrown out of wack — even in a good way — I forget the key ingredient that always makes things better. Even when I do remember, I forget the second most important part. Routine always provides me guidance. Feeling lost is one of the feelings that&amp;rsquo;s most constant in my life, and it&amp;rsquo;s one of the more unpleasant feelings that I get.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Drive Revived.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rebooted/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 19:14:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/rebooted/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve rediscovered my love for discussing society, incentives, structures, and philosophy that I encountered most while at college. And it made me realize, I can&amp;rsquo;t just listen and reflect upon the ills of society. The problems aren&amp;rsquo;t hypothetical — they involve real people that face these issues each day. Perhaps I can&amp;rsquo;t change the world, but I believe I can effect change locally. On the other hand, maybe dreaming big is worthwhile, because I should wring out any potential from the future I may have. Most importantly, it&amp;rsquo;s not enough to believe in ideals, I need to stand by them.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What If It Went Right.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/serendipity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/serendipity/</guid><description>&lt;p>About two weeks ago, I made the fun, but somewhat draining 7 hour drive from here to EDC on my own. Although I usually go to festivals with friends, I had committed to the 3-day, 32 combined hour undertaking because I was astounded the first time I went. The first view I had of the festival was incredible in its scale — tens of thousands of people, more than a dozen stages, and intricate design across the entire speedway, and I could see it all from where I stood.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Missing Dreams.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/dreams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/dreams/</guid><description>&lt;p>I don&amp;rsquo;t think I have dreams. There aren&amp;rsquo;t any specific goals I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to reach for, and I wonder if that resonates with others. Having dreams, especially distinct ones, is often portrayed in America. But perhaps as a byproduct of my aimlessness, I seem to lack any.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I want goals to aim for. I think a lack of direction is a result of vague and undefined endpoints. Having daily flexibility and stable income is not a dream — it&amp;rsquo;s more survival and not wanting to waste away precariously at a suboptimal job. I&amp;rsquo;m worried that&amp;rsquo;s my current trajectory given my lack of success in the &amp;ldquo;position acquisition&amp;rdquo; field.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Decisions.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/decisions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:44:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/decisions/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to figure out exactly what I want to do. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for jobs — with little success — and slowly draining my savings. I also read that I may have to start paying off the student loans of which I am wholly unequipped, given the above situation. What a pain.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Over the past year, I&amp;rsquo;ve told myself and others that while I&amp;rsquo;m young, I want to be flexible and not completely tied down to a place. I certainly don&amp;rsquo;t want to be tied to a job and work my life away either. I think my best course of action is rebuilding my savings, providing a buffer so I can take more risks in the future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Happier.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/happier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:31:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/happier/</guid><description>&lt;p>Life has strong ups and downs, it&amp;rsquo;s a given. I know that there is no state of being, nothing to reach that provides a constant, unending source of happiness, which seems sad. I want to reach a place in my life where I have a stable, happy life, with dips, yes, but not drop-offs where I feel aimless, depressed, and empty, for long periods. Human psychology and the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hedonic_treadmill" title="Hedonic Treadmill. | Wikipedia">hedonic treadmill&lt;/a> have proven that much.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Self-Respect &amp; Selfishness.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/respect/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 23:43:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/respect/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the journey of gaining self-respect, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to tell myself I&amp;rsquo;m being selfish. Many times when I&amp;rsquo;ve stood up for myself, I&amp;rsquo;ve been convinced that my position is unreasonable or that I&amp;rsquo;m asking for too much. So now, when I get pushback from what &lt;em>I&lt;/em> think is speaking my truth, I fold much more easily because I&amp;rsquo;m so unsure of my beliefs and not confident enough in myself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this is an excuse I tell myself, as to not become unreasonable or selfish, or instead if I&amp;rsquo;m just holding myself back with old beliefs. It&amp;rsquo;s possible that the practice of standing up for myself will make it clear what is right and what is wrong, and that as long as I am stick to my values, I don&amp;rsquo;t need to worry.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Releasing the Tethers.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tethers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:03:23 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tethers/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that what&amp;rsquo;s caused me a ton of anguish is attaching a portion of my identity to inherently unstable and impermanent states. If those states change, as they do, I find it excruciating and impossible to function, because I feel as if a portion of me is destroyed in the process. It means that I will cling to these ephemeral states and force them, even when they are due to change, always to my own detriment or the detriment of others.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Appreciation: The 'Scaring the Hoes' Album.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/appreciation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/appreciation/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="my-top-3-songs-on-scaring-the-hoes">My Top 3 Songs On &lt;em>Scaring the Hoes&lt;/em>&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="burfict---track-614">Burfict! - Track 6/14&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I really like this track because it is so bombastic straight from the beginning. Horns blaring, a thumping bass, and a really strong, addictive chorus from Danny Brown. Additionally, JPEGmafia&amp;rsquo;s flow at the start of his verse sounds great.&lt;/p>
&lt;iframe style="border: 0; width: 100%; height: 120px;" src="https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/album=3169714647/size=large/bgcol=333333/linkcol=e32c14/tracklist=false/artwork=none/track=639264020/transparent=true/" seamless>&lt;a href="https://jpegmafia.bandcamp.com/album/scaring-the-hoes">SCARING THE HOES by JPEGMAFIA x Danny Brown&lt;/a>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;h3 id="kingdom-hearts-key-ft-redveil---track-914">Kingdom Hearts Key (ft. redveil) - Track 9/14&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I think the sample on this track sounds really beautiful. It just sounds expansive, green hills all around, with bells ringing. I like all three verses, but especially the final one from redveil with a really nice beat switch. I find that the flow bounces on the beat extremely well.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Everything Can Be Found Here.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/babel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 02:38:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/babel/</guid><description>&lt;p>A long time ago I came across the &lt;a href="https://libraryofbabel.info/" title="Library of Babel">Library of Babel&lt;/a>. It&amp;rsquo;s based on a book, that I haven&amp;rsquo;t read, centered around an infinite library, containing every possible set of text imaginable. That means that although nearly all of the library contains gibberish, there are some books that contain a perfect transcript of the future, bibliographies of every human being, and any other text that can ever be written.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Taking Action.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/problems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/problems/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that I&amp;rsquo;ve had so much anxiety, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been so focused on eliminating it that when I feel normal, acceptable levels of stress, I interpret it as unnecessary and unwanted, when instead it&amp;rsquo;s more of call to action than an irrational feeling.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve gained better control over the way I feel and process stress, anxiety can feel more acute when it does happen because my brain is saying, &amp;ldquo;Why isn&amp;rsquo;t this just going away?!&amp;rdquo;. It made me realize, though, that the rational anxiety isn&amp;rsquo;t going to disappear until I deal with the source. Most of my anxiety can be cleared with perspective, yes, but some of it needs to be remedied through action.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Processing it All.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/too-much/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 13:09:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/too-much/</guid><description>&lt;p>I think it&amp;rsquo;s easy to fill compelled to capture as much knowledge as possible. I always want to go through all my RSS feeds, read every article that seems remotely interesting, and be complete by the end of the day. More information, however, just isn&amp;rsquo;t helpful. Constantly we are inundated with data and the idea that we must always be consuming. It&amp;rsquo;s accepted as the baseline, but it&amp;rsquo;s honestly exhausting to actually &lt;em>do&lt;/em>, if you think about it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>New Beliefs.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/changing-brain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:47:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/changing-brain/</guid><description>&lt;p>Over the past few months, I have done some extensive introspection. Because I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of time on my hands, it&amp;rsquo;s become much, much easier to feel every little pang that comes about, and there is much less to distract me. In that time, I&amp;rsquo;ve realized how strong this constant, incessant background anxiety was that I&amp;rsquo;ve been carrying around. Even in times of ease and safety, I still found it gripping ahold and refusing to let go.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Unsatisfying Answer.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/network-ahh/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:44:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/network-ahh/</guid><description>&lt;p>I wrote up an incomplete, 16+ paragraph discussion about the kind of social network I would like to see, before realizing that even I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I want. In my head, I want everything to be clean and tidy — one network that did everything. Created great, strong communities, answered questions about various issues, felt tight-knit and allowed for reasonable discussions, all very pie-in-the-sky. But I don&amp;rsquo;t think these can be relegated to one network, nor should they.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Accepting Different Terms.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:23:06 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/incentives/</guid><description>&lt;p>There&amp;rsquo;s been increasing scrutiny placed on social media over the past decade, from all angles. Criticisms of their practices of election meddling, attention-stealing, data collecting, and generally being cesspools of humanity. Many of these companies have created walled gardens that discourage platform departure and have been optimized to be as attention-grabbing as possible. After all, more usage generates greater revenue, even if it&amp;rsquo;s at the detriment of a beneficial experience for the user.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Reality through Perception.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/mindcontrol/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 01:06:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/mindcontrol/</guid><description>&lt;p>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to arrive at the idea that there is a significant distinction between how our brain perceives reality, and how reality actually is. It&amp;rsquo;s always been my assumption that what I&amp;rsquo;m seeing and feeling represents the reality of the situation I&amp;rsquo;m in. If I&amp;rsquo;m disappointed or frustrated, it&amp;rsquo;s because the situation is objectively disappointing or frustrating. I have come to find that this belief is often false.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When I perceive a situation, my senses attempt to provide the most accurate, objective version of reality, minimizing their own biases as much as possible. After this point, I begin to filter that data through my brain, where I began to make assertions about the situation, project my own thoughts and feelings, create nebulous connections, and personify the previously objective reality.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Intrinsic Bliss of Walking to the Store.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/walking/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 16:27:38 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/walking/</guid><description>&lt;p>Southern California is about driving. To get to &lt;em>any&lt;/em> place, you need to drive, find someone who can drive, or navigate the often slow and dismal public transit routes, all of which I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced in excess, first-hand. Although it sounds relatively negative, I enjoyed this. Driving is something I love because, especially early on in my life, it provides this immense feeling of freedom and control, despite everything else being in disarray.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>It's All In Your Head.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tools/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 14:02:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/tools/</guid><description>&lt;p>It can be difficult to identify whether anxiety can simply be overcome through thought or a shift in thinking. Given that it&amp;rsquo;s literally in the mind, what is the difference between a healthy mind and one that overthinks? Mental disorders in general are fuzzy, and somewhat undefined as they manifest differently in everyone. This can make me somewhat skeptical of our understanding of psychology because it seems so undefined, and we don&amp;rsquo;t know and can&amp;rsquo;t observe those interactions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Something Important to Me.</title><link>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 22:35:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://vault.nickbanning.com/posts/start/</guid><description>&lt;p>I used to be obsessed with the idea of legacy. This concept was pervasive — I couldn&amp;rsquo;t let go of wanting to be important or wanting to be recognized as important. This idea stuck with me for years, despite not actually working towards greatness or high achievement.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I think when you&amp;rsquo;re especially young, it can be easy to succumb to the ego and seek to defeat death, something intangible and scary. It&amp;rsquo;s great to be recognized, but I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that I just want to be satisfied with my own output and creation at the end. Legacy isn&amp;rsquo;t important because it only exists when it matters the least, and the pursuit of positive perception can only wear me down.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>